Margarita Mazo Old Believer and Molokan collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Electronic media, Floppy disk containing digital files described in the container list.; 1 floppy disk (3.5 in.) (Box-folder 8/21)
AFC 2022/003: SR055 4
AFC 2022/003: SR056 Tape 1
AFC 2022/003: SR057 Tape 2
AFC 2022/003: SR058 Tape 3
AFC 2022/003: SR059 Tape 4
AFC 2022/003: SR060 Tape 1
AFC 2022/003: SR061 Tape 2
AFC 2022/003: SR062 Tape 3
AFC 2022/003: SR063 Tape 4
AFC 2022/003: SR064 1
AFC 2022/003: SR065 2
AFC 2022/003: SR066
AFC 2022/003: SR067 STAVRO.889 DAT 1
AFC 2022/003: SR068 STAVRO.889 DAT 2
AFC 2022/003: SR069 STAVRO.889 DAT 3
AFC 2022/003: SR070 STAVRO.889 DAT 4
AFC 2022/003: SR071 STAVRO.889 DAT 5
AFC 2022/003: SR072 STAVRO.889 DAT 6
AFC 2022/003: SR073 STAVRO.889 DAT 7
AFC 2022/003: SR074 STAVRO.889 DAT 8
AFC 2022/003: SR075 STAVRO.889 DAT 9
AFC 2022/003: SR076 STAVRO.889 DAT 10
AFC 2022/003: SR077 STAVRO.889 DAT 11
AFC 2022/003: SR078 STAVRO.889 DAT 12
AFC 2022/003: SR079 STAVRO.889 DAT 13
AFC 2022/003: SR080 STAVRO.889 DAT 14
AFC 2022/003: SR081 STAVRO.889 DAT 15
AFC 2022/003: SR082 DAT 1 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR083 DAT 2 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR084 DAT 3 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR085 DAT 4 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR086 DAT 5 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR087 DAT 6 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR088 DAT 7 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR089 DAT 8 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR090 DAT 9 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR091 DAT 10 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR092 DAT 12 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR093 DAT 13 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR094 DAT 14 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR095 DAT 15 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR096 STAVRO.889 SONY 1
AFC 2022/003: SR097 STAVRO.889 SONY 2
AFC 2022/003: SR098 STAVRO.889 SONY 3
AFC 2022/003: SR099 STAVRO.889 SONY 4
AFC 2022/003: SR100 STAVRO.889 SONY 5
AFC 2022/003: SR101 STAVRO.889 SONY 6
AFC 2022/003: SR102 STAVRO.889 SONY 7
AFC 2022/003: SR103 STAVRO.889 SONY 8
AFC 2022/003: SR104 STAVRO.889 SONY 9
AFC 2022/003: SR105 STAVRO.889 SONY 10
AFC 2022/003: SR106 STAVRO.889 SONY 11
AFC 2022/003: SR107 STAVRO.889 SONY 11A
AFC 2022/003: SR108 STAVRO.889 SONY 12
AFC 2022/003: SR109 STAVRO.889 SONY 12A
AFC 2022/003: SR110 1
AFC 2022/003: SR111 2
AFC 2022/003: SR112 3
AFC 2022/003: SR113 4
AFC 2022/003: SR114 5
AFC 2022/003: SR115 6
AFC 2022/003: SR116 7
AFC 2022/003: SR117
AFC 2022/003: SR118
AFC 2022/003: SR119
AFC 2022/003: SR120
AFC 2022/003: SR121
AFC 2022/003: SR122
AFC 2022/003: SR123 STAVRO.590 SONY 1
AFC 2022/003: SR124 STAVRO.590 SONY 2
AFC 2022/003: SR125 STAVRO.590 SONY 3
AFC 2022/003: SR126 STAVRO.590 SONY 4
AFC 2022/003: SR127 STAVRO.590 SONY 5
AFC 2022/003: SR128 STAVRO.590 SONY 6
AFC 2022/003: SR129 STAVRO.590 SONY 7
AFC 2022/003: SR130 STAVRO.590 SONY 8
AFC 2022/003: SR131 STAVRO.590 SONY 9
AFC 2022/003: SR132 STAVRO.590 SONY 10
AFC 2022/003: SR133 STAVRO.590 SONY 11
AFC 2022/003: SR134 STAVRO.590 SONY 12
AFC 2022/003: SR135 STAVRO.590 SONY 13
AFC 2022/003: SR136 STAVRO.590 SONY 13A
AFC 2022/003: SR137 STAVRO.590 SONY 14
AFC 2022/003: SR138 STAVRO.590 SONY 15
AFC 2022/003: SR139 STAVRO.590 SONY 16
AFC 2022/003: SR140 STAVRO.590 SONY 17
AFC 2022/003: SR141 STAVRO.590 SONY 18
AFC 2022/003: SR142 STAVRO.590 SONY 19
AFC 2022/003: SR143 STAVRO.590 SONY 20
AFC 2022/003: SR144 STAVRO.590 SONY 21
AFC 2022/003: SR145 STAVRO.590 SONY 22
AFC 2022/003: SR146 STAVRO.590 SONY 23
AFC 2022/003: SR147 STAVRO.590 SONY 24
AFC 2022/003: SR148 STAVRO.590 SONY 25
AFC 2022/003: SR149 STAVRO.590 SONY 25 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR150 STAVRO.590 SONY 26
AFC 2022/003: SR151 STAVRO.590 SONY 26 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR152 STAVRO.590 SONY 27
AFC 2022/003: SR153 STAVRO.590 SONY 28
AFC 2022/003: SR154 STAVRO.590 SONY 28 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR155 STAVRO.590 DAT 1
AFC 2022/003: SR156 STAVRO.590 DAT 2
AFC 2022/003: SR157 STAVRO.590 DAT 3
AFC 2022/003: SR158 STAVRO.590 DAT 4
AFC 2022/003: SR159 STAVRO.590 DAT 5
AFC 2022/003: SR160 STAVRO.590 DAT 6
AFC 2022/003: SR161 STAVRO.590 DAT 7
AFC 2022/003: SR162 STAVRO.590 DAT 8
AFC 2022/003: SR163 STAVRO.590 DAT 9
AFC 2022/003: SR164 STAVRO.590 DAT 10
AFC 2022/003: SR165 STAVRO.590 DAT 11
AFC 2022/003: SR166 DAT 1 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR167 DAT 1 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR168 DAT 2 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR169 DAT 2 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR170 DAT 3 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR171 DAT 3 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR172 DAT 4 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR173 DAT 4 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR174 DAT 5 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR175 DAT 5 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR176 DAT 6 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR177 DAT 6 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR178 DAT 7 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR179 DAT 7 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR180 DAT 8 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR181 DAT 8 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR182 DAT 9 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR183 DAT 9 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR184 DAT 10 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR185
AFC 2022/003: SR186
AFC 2022/003: SR187
AFC 2022/003: SR188
AFC 2022/003: SR189
AFC 2022/003: SR190
AFC 2022/003: SR191
AFC 2022/003: SR192
AFC 2022/003: SR193
AFC 2022/003: SR194
AFC 2022/003: SR195 CALIFO.390 SONY 1
AFC 2022/003: SR196 CALIFO.390 SONY 2
AFC 2022/003: SR197 CALIFO.390 SONY 3
AFC 2022/003: SR198 CALIFO.390 SONY 4
AFC 2022/003: SR199 CALIFO.390 SONY 5
AFC 2022/003: SR200 CALIFO.390 SONY 6
AFC 2022/003: SR201 CALIFO.390 SONY 7
AFC 2022/003: SR202 CALIFO.390 SONY 8
AFC 2022/003: SR203 CALIFO.390 SONY 9
AFC 2022/003: SR204 CALIFO.390 SONY 10
AFC 2022/003: SR205 CALIFO.390 SONY 11
AFC 2022/003: SR206 CALIFO.390 SONY 12
AFC 2022/003: SR207 CALIFO.390 SONY 13
AFC 2022/003: SR208 CALIFO.390 SONY 14
AFC 2022/003: SR209 CALIFO.390 SONY 15
AFC 2022/003: SR210 CALIFO.390 SONY 16
AFC 2022/003: SR211 CALIFO.390 SONY 17
AFC 2022/003: SR212 CALIFO.390 SONY 18
AFC 2022/003: SR213 CALIFO.390 SONY 19
AFC 2022/003: SR214 CALIFO.390 SONY 20
AFC 2022/003: SR215 CALIFO.390 SONY 21
AFC 2022/003: SR216 CALIFO.390 SONY 22
AFC 2022/003: SR217 CALIFO.390 DAT 1
AFC 2022/003: SR218 CALIFO.390 DAT 2
AFC 2022/003: SR219 CALIFO.390 DAT 3
AFC 2022/003: SR220 CALIFO.390 DAT 4
AFC 2022/003: SR221 CALIFO.390 DAT 5
AFC 2022/003: SR222 CALIFO.390 DAT 6
AFC 2022/003: SR223 CALIFO.890 SONY 1
AFC 2022/003: SR224 CALIFO.890 SONY 2
AFC 2022/003: SR225 CALIFO.890 SONY 3
AFC 2022/003: SR226 CALIFO.890 SONY 4
AFC 2022/003: SR227 CALIFO.890 SONY 5
AFC 2022/003: SR228 CALIFO.890 SONY 6
AFC 2022/003: SR229 CALIFO.890 SONY 7
AFC 2022/003: SR230 CALIFO.890 SONY 8
AFC 2022/003: SR231 CALIFO.890 SONY 9
AFC 2022/003: SR232 CALIFO.890 SONY 10
AFC 2022/003: SR233 CALIFO.890 SONY 11
AFC 2022/003: SR234 CALIFO.890 SONY 12
AFC 2022/003: SR235 CALIFO.890 SONY 13
AFC 2022/003: SR236 CALIFO.890 SONY 14
AFC 2022/003: SR237 CALIFO.890 SONY 15
AFC 2022/003: SR238 CALIFO.890 SONY 16
AFC 2022/003: SR239 CALIFO.890 SONY 17
AFC 2022/003: SR240 CALIFO.890 SONY 18
AFC 2022/003: SR241 CALIFO.890 SONY 19
AFC 2022/003: SR242 CALIFO.890 SONY 20
AFC 2022/003: SR243 CALIFO.890 SONY 20A
AFC 2022/003: SR244 CALIFO.890 SONY 21
AFC 2022/003: SR245 CALIFO.890 SONY 22
AFC 2022/003: SR246 CALIFO.890 SONY 23
AFC 2022/003: SR247 CALIFO.890 SONY 24
AFC 2022/003: SR248 CALIFO.890 SONY 25
AFC 2022/003: SR249 CALIFO.890 SONY 26
AFC 2022/003: SR250 CALIFO.890 SONY 27
AFC 2022/003: SR251 CALIFO.890 SONY 28
AFC 2022/003: SR252 CALIFO.890 SONY 29
AFC 2022/003: SR253 CALIFO.890 SONY 30
AFC 2022/003: SR254 CALIFO.890 DAT 1
AFC 2022/003: SR255 CALIFO.890 DAT 2
AFC 2022/003: SR256 CALIFO.890 DAT 3
AFC 2022/003: SR257 CALIFO.890 DAT 4
AFC 2022/003: SR258 CALIFO.890 DAT 5
AFC 2022/003: SR259 CALIFO.890 DAT 6
AFC 2022/003: SR260 DAT 1 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR261 DAT 1 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR262 DAT 2 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR263 DAT 2 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR264 DAT 2 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR265 DAT 3 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR266 DAT 5 copy
AFC 2022/003: SR267 1
AFC 2022/003: SR268 2
AFC 2022/003: SR269 2B
AFC 2022/003: SR270 3
AFC 2022/003: SR271 4
AFC 2022/003: SR272 4B
AFC 2022/003: SR273 5
AFC 2022/003: SR274 6
AFC 2022/003: SR275
AFC 2022/003: SR276
AFC 2022/003: SR277
AFC 2022/003: SR278 1
AFC 2022/003: SR279 2
AFC 2022/003: SR280 2b
AFC 2022/003: SR281 19
AFC 2022/003: SR282
AFC 2022/003: SR283
AFC 2022/003: SR284
AFC 2022/003: SR285
AFC 2022/003: SR286
AFC 2022/003: SR287
AFC 2022/003: SR288
AFC 2022/003: SR289
AFC 2022/003: SR290
AFC 2022/003: SR291
AFC 2022/003: SR292
AFC 2022/003: SR293
AFC 2022/003: SR294
AFC 2022/003: SR295
AFC 2022/003: SR296
AFC 2022/003: SR297
AFC 2022/003: SR298 1
AFC 2022/003: SR299 2
AFC 2022/003: SR300 DAT 1
AFC 2022/003: SR301 DAT 2
AFC 2022/003: SR302 DAT 3
AFC 2022/003: SR303 DAT 4
AFC 2022/003: SR304 SONY 1
AFC 2022/003: SR305 SONY 2
AFC 2022/003: SR306 SONY 3
AFC 2022/003: SR307 SONY 4
AFC 2022/003: SR308 SONY 5
AFC 2022/003: SR309 SONY 5A
AFC 2022/003: SR310 SONY 6
AFC 2022/003: SR311 SONY 6A
AFC 2022/003: SR312 SONY 7
AFC 2022/003: SR313 SONY 8
AFC 2022/003: SR314 SONY 9
AFC 2022/003: SR315 SONY 10A
AFC 2022/003: SR316 SONY 11
AFC 2022/003: SR317 SONY 12
AFC 2022/003: SR318 SONY 13
AFC 2022/003: SR319 SONY 14
AFC 2022/003: SR320 SONY 15
AFC 2022/003: SR321 SONY 16
AFC 2022/003: SR322 SONY 17
AFC 2022/003: SR323 SONY 18
AFC 2022/003: SR324
AFC 2022/003: SR325 Master 1
AFC 2022/003: SR326 1a
AFC 2022/003: SR327 2
AFC 2022/003: SR328 3
AFC 2022/003: SR329 Sony 4
AFC 2022/003: SR330 5
AFC 2022/003: SR331 6
AFC 2022/003: SR332 7
AFC 2022/003: SR333 DAT 1
AFC 2022/003: SR334 DAT 2
AFC 2022/003: SR335 DAT 3
AFC 2022/003: SR336 DAT 4
AFC 2022/003: SR337 1
AFC 2022/003: SR338 2
AFC 2022/003: SR339 3
AFC 2022/003: SR340 4
AFC 2022/003: SR341 5
AFC 2022/003: SR342 1
AFC 2022/003: SR343 2
AFC 2022/003: SR344
AFC 2022/003: SR345
AFC 2022/003: SR346
AFC 2022/003: SR347
AFC 2022/003: SR348 1
AFC 2022/003: SR349 2
AFC 2022/003: SR350 3
AFC 2022/003: SR351 4
AFC 2022/003: SR352 5
AFC 2022/003: SR353
AFC 2022/003: SR354
AFC 2022/003: SR355
AFC 2022/003: SR356
AFC 2022/003: SR357 1
AFC 2022/003: SR358 2
AFC 2022/003: SR359 1
AFC 2022/003: SR360 2
AFC 2022/003: SR361 4
AFC 2022/003: SR362 5
AFC 2022/003: SR363
AFC 2022/003: SR364 1
AFC 2022/003: SR365 2
AFC 2022/003: SR366 1
AFC 2022/003: SR367 2
AFC 2022/003: SR368 3
AFC 2022/003: SR369
AFC 2022/003: SR370
AFC 2022/003: SR371
AFC 2022/003: SR372
AFC 2022/003: SR373
AFC 2022/003: SR374
AFC 2022/003: SR375
AFC 2022/003: SR376
AFC 2022/003: SR377
AFC 2022/003: SR378
AFC 2022/003: SR379
AFC 2022/003: SR380
AFC 2022/003: SR381
AFC 2022/003: SR382
AFC 2022/003: SR383
AFC 2022/003: SR384 1
AFC 2022/003: SR385 2
AFC 2022/003: SR386 3
AFC 2022/003: SR387 4
AFC 2022/003: SR388 5
AFC 2022/003: SR389 6
AFC 2022/003: SR390 1
AFC 2022/003: SR391 2
AFC 2022/003: SR392
AFC 2022/003: SR393
AFC 2022/003: SR394